Inventory of the Resistencia Nicaragüense Ejército records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Vicente case: memorandum, interrogation report (Seguridad del Estado Mayor, Sección de Personal), 1989 (Box-folder 26: 12)
- Zapollon case: investigative reports, memoranda, interrogation reports (Seguridad del Estado Mayor, Sección de Personal), 1989 (Box-folder 26: 13)
- Ex-Guardia Nacional personnel: memorandum, 1989 (Box-folder 26: 14)
- Ex-Sandinista personnel: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 26: 15)
- Recruits: lists, memoranda, messages, 1987 (Box-folder 26: 16)
- Organization, Centro de Instrucción Militar, Miscellany: charts, training curriculum, miscellaneous memoranda, map, miscellany, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 26: 17)
- Organization, Miscellany: charts, memoranda, miscellany, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 26: 18)
- Organization, Sección de Contrainteligencia: charts, memorandum, 1989 (Box-folder 26: 19)
- Organization, Miscellany: chart, miscellany, 1989 (Box-folder 26: 20)
- Commanding officers, state of force: lists, reports, 1985 (Box-folder 26: 21)
- Commanding officers: lists, personnel data sheets, 1986 (Box-folder 26: 22)
- Commanding officers, state of force: lists, reports, 1986 (Box-folder 26: 23)
- Commanding officers: lists, 1987 (Box-folder 26: 24)
- Commanding officers, Miscellany: lists, memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 26: 25)
- Commanding officers, Miscellany: lists, memoranda, personnel data sheets, 1988 (Box-folder 27: 1)
- Commanding officers: lists, organizational table, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 27: 2)
- Commanding officers: lists, personnel data sheets, 1989 (Box-folder 27: 3)
- Commanding officers: lists, memorandum, 1989 (Box-folder 27: 4)
- Commanding officers: list, 1989 (Box-folder 27: 5)
- Commanding officers: lists, memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 27: 6-7)
- Commanding officers: lists, organizational table, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 27: 8)
- Commanding officers, Sección de Inteligencia, Sección de Personal, Miscellany: lists, memoranda, messages, 1990 (Box-folder 27: 9)
- Commanding officers: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 27: 10)
- Organization: photographs of personnel arranged by unit, undated (Box-folder 27: 11)
- Representatives to United Nations: list, 1987 (Box-folder 27: 12)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: lists, blank forms, 1990 (Box-folder 27: 13)
- Personnel demobilized, personnel repatriated: list, 1991 (Box-folder 27: 14)
- State of force: reports, 1982 (Box-folder 27: 15)
- State of force, combat: reports, memoranda, pamphlet, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 27: 16-17)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, personnel data sheets, Base Escuela roster, Grupo Quilambo roster, personnel lists, miscellany, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 27: 18)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, memoranda, Grupo Musún roster, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 28: 1)
- State of force, personnel actions, Miscellany: reports, memoranda, miscellany, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 28: 2)
- State of force, equipment, Miscellany: reports, inventory, memoranda, bulletin, miscellany, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 28: 3)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 28: 4-5)
- State of force, combat, personnel actions: reports, miscellany, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 28: 6-7)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, proclamations, memoranda, bulletin, miscellany, 1984 (Box-folder 28: 8)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, personnel data sheets, personnel lists, memoranda, notes, miscellany, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 28: 9)
- State of force, Clínicas Médicas, Miscellany: reports, patient lists, personnel lists, messages, 1987 (Box-folder 28: 10)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, Seguridad del Estado Mayor roster, messages, 1987 (Box-folder 28: 11)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, rosters, personnel lists, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 28: 12)
- State of force: reports, messages, 1988 (Box-folder 28: 13)
- State of force: reports, 1988 (3 folders) (Box-folder 29: 1-3)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, munitions inventory, weapons assignment lists, 1988 (Box-folder 29: 4)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, rosters, 1988 (Box-folder 29: 5)
- State of force: reports, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 29: 6-7)
- State of force: reports, 1989 (Box-folder 29: 8)
- State of force: reports, memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 29: 9)
- State of force, Miscellany: reports, personnel lists, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 29: 10-11)
- State of force: reports, 1990 (Box-folder 29: 12-13)
- Dependents, humanitarian aid: lists, letters, 1983 (Box-folder 29: 14)
- Dependents: lists, memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 29: 15)
- Humanitarian aid: recipient lists, 1988 (Box-folder 29: 16)
- Humanitarian aid, Sección de Logistica, Sección de Personal: lists, memoranda, regulations, 1988 (Box-folder 29: 17)
- Humanitarian aid: recipient lists, 1989 (Box-folder 30: 1)
- Humanitarian aid: recipient lists, receipts, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 30: 3)
- Humanitarian aid: recipient lists, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 30: 3)
- Humanitarian aid: recipient lists, 1990 (Box-folder 30: 4-7)
- Humanitarian aid, mothers of personnel killed, orphans, demobilized personnel: lists, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 30: 8)
- Humanitarian aid: recipient lists, undated (Box-folder 30: 9)
- Humanitarian aid, Clínicas Médicas: memoranda, roster, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 30: 10)
- Humanitarian aid: memorandum, 1988 (Box-folder 30: 11)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: memorandum, miscellany, 1988 (Box-folder 30: 12)
- Humanitarian aid: memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 30: 13-14)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: memoranda, personnel list, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 30: 15)
- Humanitarian aid: memoranda, receipt, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 30: 16)
- Humanitarian aid, contacts in Honduras, Miscellany: authorization, list, miscellany, 1984 (Box-folder 30: 17)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, 1988 (Box-folder 30: 18-19)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, 1988 (Box-folder 31: 1-3)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: authorizations, recipient lists, marriage license, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 31: 4)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 31: 5)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, 1989 (Box-folder 31: 6-11)
- Humanitarian aid, equipment: authorizations, requisition, 1989 (Box-folder 32: 1-2)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: authorizations, messages, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32: 3)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 32: 4-6)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 7-10)
- Humanitarian aid: authorizations, recipient lists, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 11-12)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: authorizations, identification card, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 13)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: authorization, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 14)
- Humanitarian aid (Danlí): authorizations, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 15)
- Humanitarian aid (El Paraíso): authorizations, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 16)
- Humanitarian aid (Las Trojes): authorizations, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 17)
- Humanitarian aid, Miscellany: receipts, authorizations, recipient lists, miscellany, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 32: 18)
- Humanitarian aid, immigration, Nicaraguan exile organizations: receipts, memoranda, directory, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 32: 19)
- Humanitarian aid, asylum: receipts, recipient lists, application, certifications of service, 1989 (Box-folder 32: 20)
- Humanitarian aid: withdrawals of authorization, 1990 (Box-folder 32: 21)
- Agency for International Development: training course rosters (Centro de Capacitacion Administrativo Rafaela Herrera), 1990 (Box-folder 33: 1)
- Literacy course: rosters, 1987 (Box-folder 33: 2)
- Literacy course: workbook, 1989 (Box-folder 33: 3)
- Agency for International Development: humanitarian aid program reports, 1988 (Box-folder 33: 4)
- Agency for International Development, Estado Mayor: humanitarian aid program report, memoranda, service depositions, invoices, munitions lists, miscellany, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 33: 5)
- Agency for International Development, Fiscalía Militar: humanitarian aid program report, service depositions, press visit authorizations, letters, memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 33: 6)
- Sección de Personal, other units: humanitarian aid program reports, recipient lists, memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 33: 7)
- Coordinadora General de Ayuda Humanitaria, other units: humanitarian aid program reports, memoranda, letters, 1989 (Box-folder 33: 8)
- Coordinadora General de Ayuda Humanitaria: food allotment chart, undated (Box-folder 33: 9)
- Economic development: proposals, undated (Box-folder 33: 10)
- Asylum (United States), Miscellany: application, miscellany, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 33: 11)
- Asylum (United States), missing persons, Miscellany: application, identification documents, personnel lists, lists, reports, memoranda, letters, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 33: 12)
- Asylum (United States): application, 1989 (Box-folder 33: 13)
- Immigration: application lists, undated (Box-folder 33: 14)
- Immigration: application information, blank forms, undated (Box-folder 33: 15)
- Contacts in United States, missing persons: memoranda, correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 33: 16)
- Agency for International Development: lists of contractors, 1990 (Box-folder 33: 17)
- Contacts in United States: addresses and telephone numbers, undated (Box-folder 33: 18)
- Unidentified and miscellaneous units: rosters, weapons assignment lists, miscellaneous personnel lists, 1987 (Box-folder 34: 1)
- Personnel with long service: lists, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 34: 2)
- Female personnel: lists, 1985 (Box-folder 34: 3)
- Female personnel: lists, 1987 (Box-folder 34: 4)
- Female personnel: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 34: 5-6)
- Female personnel, children, Miscellany: lists, receipts, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 34: 7)
- Female personnel, children, other dependents: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 34: 8)
- Children: lists, 1988 (Box-folder 34: 9-10)
- Children, Miscellany: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 34: 11)
- Children, contacts in Honduras: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 34: 12)
- Children, Miscellany: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 34: 13)
- Dependent refugees: lists, 1987 (Box-folder 34: 14)
- Civilian refugees, Miscellany: lists, ration card, 1988 (Box-folder 34: 15)
- Civilian refugees, humanitarian aid, equipment, Miscellany: lists, memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 34: 16)
- Dependent refugees: lists, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 34: 17)
- Civilian refugees: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 34: 18)
- Personnel granted leave: list, undated (Box-folder 34: 19)
- Personnel granted leave: logbook, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 35: 1)
- Visitors: logsheets, 1991 (Box-folder 35: 2)
- Visitors: logbook, 1992 (Box-folder 35: 3)
- Visitors: logbook, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 35: 4)
- Unidentified personnel: photographs, miscellaneous identification cards, miscellaneous memoranda, undated (Box-folder 35: 5-7)
- Unidentified personnel: negatives, undated (Box-folder 36)
- Codes, Miscellany: code key, note, undated (Box-folder 37: 1)
- Americas Watch, Oficina de Asesoría Legal: human rights report, memorandum re code of conduct, 1988 (Box-folder 37: 2)
- Americas Watch: human rights report, clippings, 1989 (Box-folder 37: 3)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Amnesty International, Americas Watch, Oficina de Asesoría Legal: human rights reports, memoranda, letters, code of conduct, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 37: 4)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Consejo de Comandantes, Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: human rights reports, memoranda, peace process proposals, agreements, communiques, letters, notes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 37: 5)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: human rights report, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 37: 6)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: human rights memoranda, letters, 1988 (Box-folder 37: 7)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Estado Mayor: human rights memoranda, letters, military tribunal decision (Quilalí case), 1989 (Box-folder 37: 8)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Estado Mayor: human rights memoranda, letters, miscellaneous messages, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 37: 9)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Sección de Personal: lists of human rights officers, memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 37: 10)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Sección de Personal: lists of human rights officers, 1989 (Box-folder 37: 11)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: human rights training program curriculum and schedule, 1988 (Box-folder 37: 12)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Sección de Personal: human rights training program curriculum and schedules, lists of human rights trainees, 1989 (Box-folder 37: 13)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of prisoners released by Sandinistas, lists of prisoners not released, 1989 (Box-folder 38: 1)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of prisoners of Sandinistas, list of prisoners released, list of prisoners not released, 1989 (Box-folder 38: 2)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of prisoners of Sandinistas, 1989 (Box-folder 38: 3-4)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of prisoners released by Sandinistas, 1989 (Box-folder 38: 5)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: list of prisoners released by Sandinistas, list of prisoners scheduled to be released, 1989 (Box-folder 38: 6)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of missing persons, 1988 (Box-folder 38: 7)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of missing persons, human rights reports, 1988 (Box-folder 38: 8)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of missing persons, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 39: 1)
- Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of missing persons, blank forms, 1989 (Box-folder 39: 2)
- Sandinista human rights violations: lists, blank forms, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 39: 3)
- Sandinista human rights violations: lists, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 39: 4)
- Sandinista human rights violations: reports, 1989 (Box-folder 39: 5)
- Sandinista human rights violations: lists, statistics (Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas), 1990 (Box-folder 39: 6-7)
- Prisoners of Sandinistas: lists, 1988 (Box-folder 39: 8)
- Prisoners of Sandinistas: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 39: 9-11)
- Red Cross: memoranda re human rights monitoring, 1990 (Box-folder 39: 12)
- Oficina de Asesoría Legal, Sección de Contrainteligencia, Sección de Personal: human rights reports, memoranda, messages, lists of human rights officers, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 39: 13)
- Human rights: Sandinista pamphlet, miscellany, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 39: 14)
- Sección de Personal, Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos: lists of personnel reported by Sandinistas as abducted, 1989 (Box-folder 39: 15)
- Human rights monitors: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 39: 16)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: lists, 1987 (Box-folder 39: 17)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: lists, 1990 (Box-folder 39: 18-19)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned, children, state of force: lists, reports, 1990 (Box-folder 39: 20)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: logs, statistics, 1985 (Box-folder 39: 21)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: logs, statistics, 1986 (Box-folder 39: 22)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: logs, statistics, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 39: 23)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: logs, statistics, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 40: 1)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned: logs, 1990 (Box-folder 40: 2)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned, state of force, commanding officers: statistics, reports, list, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 3)
- Personnel infiltrated and returned, personnel discharged, deserters: statistics, 1989 (Box-folder 40: 4)
- Border control: memoranda, list, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 40: 5)
- Border control (Danlí): memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 40: 6)
- Intelligence: report, personnel data sheet (Sección de Inteligencia), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 40: 7)
- Intelligence: report (Sección de Inteligencia), 1988 (Box-folder 40: 8)
- Intelligence: reports (Sección de Inteligencia), 1989 (Box-folder 40: 9)
- Intelligence: reports, memoranda (Sección de Inteligencia, Sección de Contrainteligencia), 1989 (Box-folder 40: 10)
- Intelligence, human rights, Miscellany: reports, memoranda (Estado Mayor, Sección de Personal, Sección de Inteligencia, Sección de Contrainteligencia), 1989 (Box-folder 40: 11)
- Intelligence, peace process, Miscellany: reports, communiques, letter, clippings (Sección de Inteligencia, United Nations), 1989 (Box-folder 40: 12)
- Sección de Inteligencia: regulations, undated (Box-folder 40: 13)
- Intelligence, munitions, Miscellany: memoranda, lists (Comando Estratégico), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 40: 14)
- Intelligence: memorandum, 1990 (Box-folder 40: 15)
- Intelligence: memorandum, undated (Box-folder 40: 16)
- Supplies: requisitions, 1987 (Box-folder 40: 17)
- Supplies, Miscellany: requisitions, lists, memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 40: 18)
- Supplies, equipment, munitions: requisitions, lists, inventories, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 40: 19)
- Supplies: requisitions, 1990 (Box-folder 40: 20-21)
- Supplies: lists, 1989 (Box-folder 40: 22-24)
- Supplies: expenditure reports, receipt, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 40: 25)
- Supplies: expenditure reports, 1990 (Box-folder 40: 26)
- Supplies: receipts, 1989 (Box-folder 40: 27)
- Supplies: receipts, 1990 (Box-folder 40: 28)
- Motor vehicles: inventories, personnel memoranda (Sección de Transporte), 1986 (Box-folder 40: 29)
- Munitions, supplies: inventories, lists, receipts, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 40: 30)
- Munitions, equipment, personnel infiltrated and returned: inventories, log, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 40: 31)
- Logistics, equipment, human rights, electoral process: reports, inventories (Base San Andrés de Bocay, Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Americas Watch), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 40: 32)
- Logistics, equipment, commanding officers: reports, inventories, lists (Base San Andrés de Bocay, Cuerpo Médico, Estado Mayor, miscellaneous units), 1990 (Box-folder 40: 33)
- Message traffic: messages, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 34)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 41 to 45)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 46: 1)
- Message traffic: messages, memoranda, 1989 March-April (Box-folder 46: 2)
- Message traffic: messages, 1989 April (Box-folder 46: 3)
- Message traffic: memoranda, 1989 January-April (Box-folder 46: 4)
- Message traffic, Miscellany: memoranda, personnel lists, miscellany, 1989 April-June (Box-folder 46: 5)
- Miscellany: memorandum, note, 1989 April-June (Box-folder 46: 6)
- Message traffic, Miscellany: memoranda, 1988-1989 (mainly 1989 April-July) (Box-folder 46: 7)
- Message traffic: messages, 1989 September-1990 January (Box-folder 47: 1)
- Miscellany: letters, 1989 (Box-folder 47: 2)
- Miscellany: memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 47: 3)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 January (Box-folder 47: 4)
- Message traffic, peace process violations: messages, 1990 January (Box-folder 47: 5)
- Message traffic: memoranda, 1990 January (3 folders) (Box-folder 47: 6-8)
- Miscellany, human rights: memoranda, reports, 1989-1990 (mainly 1990 January) (Box-folder 47: 9)
- Miscellany, expenditures, dependents repatriated: memoranda, reports, list, letters, 1989-1990 (mainly 1990 January) (Box-folder 47: 10)
- Message traffic: memoranda, 1990 January-March (Box-folder 47: 11-12)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 January-April (Box-folder 47: 13)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 January-April (3 folders) (Box-folder 48: 1-3)
- Message traffic: messages, miscellany, 1990 January-April (Box-folder 48: 4)
- Message traffic: memoranda, 1990 January-April (Box-folder 48: 5-6)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 February (Box-folder 48: 7-9)
- Message traffic: memoranda, 1990 February-March (Box-folder 48: 10)
- Message traffic, Miscellany: memoranda, personnel lists, 1990 February-June (Box-folder 48: 11)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 March (Box-folder 48: 12-14)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 March (Box-folder 49: 1)
- Message traffic, Miscellany: messages, miscellany, 1989-1990 (mainly 1990 March) (Box-folder 49: 2-3)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 April (Box-folder 49: 4-5)
- CLOSED (Box-folder 49: 6)
- Message traffic: messages, 1990 April-May (Box-folder 49: 7)
- Combat: statistics, 1985 (Box-folder 49: 8)
- Combat: reports, 1987 (Box-folder 49: 9)
- Combat: statistics, 1989 (Box-folder 49: 10-11)
- Combat: reports, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 49: 12)
- Combat: statistics, 1990 (Box-folder 49: 13-14)
- Combat, human rights: statistics, notes, photographs, 1990 (Box-folder 49: 15)
- Combat: reports, 1990 (Box-folder 49: 16)
- Peace process, human rights: agreements, proposals, position papers, memoranda, studies, statutes, letters, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 49: 17)
- Peace process: agreements, proposals, communiques, letters, 1988 (Box-folder 49: 18)
- Peace process: agreements, proposals, communiques, letters, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 49: 19)
- Peace process: agreements, communiques, memoranda, negotiation summaries, speeches, legal briefs, financial records, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 49: 20)
- Peace process violations: reports, statistics, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 1)
- Peace process violations: reports, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 2)
- Peace process violations: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 3)
- Electoral process, peace process, human rights: proposals, position papers, speech, memoranda, letter, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 50: 4)
- Electoral process: agreement, proposals, statutes, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 50: 5)
- Electoral process, peace process, human rights: proposals, report, position papers, memoranda, letter, clipping (Asociación Nicaragüense Pro-Derechos Humanos, Freedom House), 1988 (Box-folder 50: 6)
- Electoral process, peace process: memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 50: 7)
- Electoral process: memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 50: 8-12)
- Electoral process: voter registration sheets (Coalición Pro Derechos del Exilio Nicaragüense), 1989 (Box-folder 50: 13)
- Electoral process: messages, 1989 (Box-folder 50: 14)
- Electoral process, political parties: messages, 1ist, 1989 (Box-folder 50: 15)
- Electoral process: agreement, position papers, communiques, press releases, memoranda, letters, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 50: 16)
- Electoral process: memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 50: 17)
- Electoral process: messages, memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 50: 18)
- Electoral process: agreement, proposals, letters, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 19)
- Electoral process: communiques, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 20)
- Electoral process: political meeting reports, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 21)
- Electoral process: letters, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 22)
- Electoral process: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 50: 23-26)
- Electoral process, peace process: proposals, miscellany, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 50: 27)
- Electoral process violations: reports, messages, 1989 (Box-folder 51: 1)
- Electoral process violations: messages, 1990 (Box-folder 51: 2-3)
- Electoral process disarmament compliance: memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 51: 4)
- Electoral process disarmament compliance: press release, memoranda, letter (Comision Internacional de Apoyo y Verificacion), 1990 (Box-folder 51: 5)
- Asociación Libro Libre: bibliography, undated (Box-folder 51: 6)
- Miscellany: manifesto, 1982 (Box-folder 51: 7)
- Public relations, Miscellany: press releases, biographical data, photographs, letter, miscellany, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 51: 8)
- Public relations, press visits, Miscellany: communique, declaration, letter, photograph, identification document, authorization, miscellany, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 51: 9)
- Public relations, Miscellany: communiques, pamphlet, position paper, memoranda, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 51: 10)
- Public relations, Miscellany: communiques, proclamation, memoranda, letters, clippings, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 51: 11)
- Miscellany: proclamation, 1988 (Box-folder 51: 12)
- Public relations, combat: communiques, agreement, statistics, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 51: 13)
- Public relations: communiques, 1989 (Box-folder 51: 14)
- Public relations: communiques, letters, 1989 (Box-folder 51: 15)
- Public relations: communiques, memoranda, 1989 (Box-folder 51: 16)